<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>!! TBOI: Rekindled</name>
    <directory>!! rekindled</directory>
    <id>2761134241</id>
    <description>[h1]What is Tboi Rekindled?[/h1]
This is a massive modpack with over 350 visual-upgrading mods, a small handful of gameplay oriented mods and plenty new custom changes/tweaks/sprites.
A long while ago I compiled the modpack for myself, but I eventually decided to share it with the community, due to how much effort has been put into it. Over time, I've been adding alot of my own created content, not found in any other mods, to make TR feel unique and special.

To clarify something rather important: A solid 75% of TR's contents are not made/owned by me, I have credited each individual mod and their creators via the linked collection. 
This was created to build upon the TBOI experience while avoiding the lag that comes with subscribing to an immense amount of mods. It also goes without saying, an equally large focus of TR is to make all the mods included completely compatible with one another and for the modpack as a whole to be compatible with the most popular mods on the Steam Workshop.

These are the gameplay mods are relatively minor changes but feel very vanilla nonetheless (The majority are toggleable via mod config menu):
- Amazing Chest Ahead (No Haunted Items)
- Blue Womb Improved
- Bomb-able Devil Statues (Balanced Better)
- Centered Fallen Angels
- Coin Flip
- Double Spiked Rocks (Just Spikes)
- Enemy Blood Donations
- Enhancement Chamber (Some Rooms)
- Fallen Gabriel spawns an imp instead of an angelic baby
- Giant Props!
- Glitchfast: Breakfasting Replaced with Glitch Items
- HUD Toggle
- Hush's Item Pool
- Item Chests Before Mother (2 Chests)
- Minisaac for Mom
- Seven Floors of Bad Luck (No Glass Cannon)

[h1]Extra Details:[/h1]
Firstly, if any of the included mod creators want me to adjust or remove content, feel free to ask. Secondly, TR is maintainted by a small team of 2 people so please be patient when waiting for updates, although, we will be updating this regularly with every new worthwhile addition that is found, both new and old (FYI, we don't include joke/meme mods of any kind but if you have a suggestion for others that you'd like to see added, please use the discussion thread). Lastly, it's advised that you unsubscribe from mods that are already within TR, as some will cause errors/issues (And, loading multiple versions of the same mod is redundant).

Required Mods:
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3127536138] Repentogon [/url] is needed for TBOI: Rekindled to function.

Recommended Mods:
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2851063440] Fiend Folio [/url]
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2847697646] Improved and Reworked Foes [/url]
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1978904635] MiniMAPI [/url]
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2974704582] Fall from Grace [/url]
- [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3343815332] Last Judgement [/url]
(TR has extra built-in compatibility with these).

[h1]Thank You![/h1]
To all the mod creators out there, I extend my gratitude to you. Thanks for constantly breathing new life into the game, keeping it fresh and interesting to play, year after year, since it's release back in 2014. The Binding Of Isaac alongside it's thriving community is made better constantly via what you all make and innovate upon, and I hope it continues for the forseeable future.
[img]https://i.imgur.com/81eM7ky.png[/img]</description>
    <version>1.136</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Hazards"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Removals"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Shaders"/>
    <tag id="Sound Effects"/>
    <tag id="Music"/>
</metadata>
