<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>!! TBOI: Rekindled</name>
    <directory>!! rekindled</directory>
    <id>2761134241</id>
    <description>[h1]What is Tboi Rekindled?[/h1]
TR is a massive modpack with almost 300 GFX/visual upgrading mods (and a small handful of gameplay addition mods as well). 
Ages ago, I originally compiled it for myself but I eventually decided to share it with the community, due to how much effort has been put into it. Over time, I've been adding alot of my own sprites and tweaks, not found in any other mods, to make it really feel like its own thing as well.
Nonetheless, I would like to clarify something rather important: A solid 80% of the content within TR is not made by me, and neither do I claim that it is. The main goal of this mod is to build upon the vanilla TBOI experience while avoiding the lag that comes with downloading an immense amount of mods.
And it goes without saying, all the mods included have been made completely compatible with one another (And the modpack itself is compatible with every major content mod).

Here are the gameplay addition mods, I consider them to be relatively minor changes but I also believe they are worthy of being added into the main game:
- Amazing Chest Ahead (No Haunted Chest Items)
- Bell Chime for Good Items
- Blue Womb Improved
- Bomb-able Devil Statues (Balanced Better)
- Centered Fallen Angels
- Coin Flip
- Enemy Blood Donations
- Fallen Gabriel spawns an imp instead of an angelic baby
- Glitchfast: Breakfasting Replaced with Glitch Items
- HUD Toggle
- Item Chests Before Mother (Only 2 Chests)
- Seven Floors of Bad Luck (No Glass Cannon)
- ??? Pill Rename

Feel free to check the linked collection below to see all the specific mods within the pack too.
If you have a suggestion for a mod that you'd like to see added, please use the suggestions discussion thread.

[h1]Modpack Details:[/h1]
Firstly, if any of the included mod creators want me to adjust or remove content, feel free to ask. Secondly, TR is maintainted by a small team of 2 people so please be patient when waiting for updates, although, we will be updating this regularly with every new worthwhile addition that is found, both new and old (FYI, we don't include joke/meme mods of any kind). Lastly, it's advised that you unsubscribe from any mod that is already included in TR, as some will cause errors (plus, loading multiple versions of the same mod is redundant).

Required Mods:
- Repentogon is needed for TBOI: Rekindled to function.
- Custom Stage API is needed for Missing Tears GFX to function.

Recommended Mods:
- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3319873865
(These are unable to be added to TR).

Known Issues &amp; Incompatibilities:
- Detailed Respawn [REP] makes the health UI invisible.

[h1]Thank You![/h1]
To all the mod creators out there, I extend my gratitude to you. Thanks for constantly breathing new life into the game, keeping it fresh and interesting to play, via innovation. The Binding Of Isaac alongside it's thriving community is made better every day with all the things that are newly created and I hope it continues for the forseeable future.
[img]https://i.imgur.com/81eM7ky.png[/img]</description>
    <version>1.132</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Shaders"/>
    <tag id="Sound Effects"/>
    <tag id="Music"/>
</metadata>
